{
  "shortDescription": "Quiz on the functioning of Dappykit.",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What is Dappykit?",
      "answers": ["Tool", "OS", "Game"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Dappykit helps to build?",
      "answers": ["dApps", "Sites", "Games"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Dappykit is used for?",
      "answers": ["Blockchain", "AI", "VR"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which layer does Dappykit support?",
      "answers": ["Layer 2", "Layer 1", "Layer 3"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Dappykit aids in?",
      "answers": ["Testing", "Mining", "Trading"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Dappykit supports?",
      "answers": ["Web3", "Web2", "Web1"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What tech is central to Dappykit?",
      "answers": ["Smart", "BigData", "Cloud"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Dappykit optimizes?",
      "answers": ["dApps", "Sites", "Files"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Dappykit offers?",
      "answers": ["SDK", "API", "GUI"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Primary use of Dappykit?",
      "answers": ["Dev", "Admin", "User"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Dappykit enhances?",
      "answers": ["UX", "UX/UI", "UI"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Dappykit focuses on?",
      "answers": ["Web3", "Web2", "Web"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Dappykit is?",
      "answers": ["Modular", "Linear", "Fixed"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Dappykit integrates?",
      "answers": ["Smart", "Dumb", "Hard"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Dappykit provides?",
      "answers": ["Lib", "Tools", "Packs"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Dappykit is written in?",
      "answers": ["Solidity", "Python", "C++"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Dappykit uses?",
      "answers": ["DeFi", "CeFi", "HyFi"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Dappykit supports?",
      "answers": ["dApps", "APIs", "Nodes"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Dappykit enables?",
      "answers": ["Deploy", "Design", "Debug"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Dappykit runs on?",
      "answers": ["Node", "React", "Angular"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    }
  ]
}
